A Guide to the Han Schroeder Architectural Collection, 1914-1992
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Project Records, 1914-1975
  - Project 38. Jr. B. Schroeder ( Veldweg [29], Hattem, The Netherlands; 1957; House ) (Box-folder 2:21-22, Box-folder 7:2, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 14, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 7, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 6, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 5, Box-folder 3:1-2)
  - Project 39. "Stichting Humanitas van Ellecom" Humanitarian Foundation of Ellecom ( Kastanjelaan, Ellecom, The Netherlands; 1975; Executive Residence ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 3)
  - Project 40. Dr. Elias ( Sportlaan, The Hague, The Netherlands; 1957; House ) (Box-folder 1:34, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 3)
  - Project 41. Fam. Smitskamp ( Johannes Verhulststraat 199, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1958; Renovation ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 3, Box-folder 3:4)
  - Project 42. Mevr. Smit ( Bussumerweg, Blaricum, The Netherlands; 1958; House ) (Box-folder 7:2, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 3, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 2, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 3 / Folder 1)
  - Project 43. Dr. Olivier ( Keucheniusstraat 15, Amstelveen, The Netherlands; 1958-1959 ) (Box-folder 3:7, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 10)
  - Project 44. Mevr. T. Smit ( Weesperzijde 6, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1958-1959; House ) (Box-folder 7:2, Box 3:8, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 10)
  - Project 45. Fam. Goemans ( Slotlaan 94, Zeist, The Netherlands; 1958-1962; Renovation ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 9, Box-folder 5:2-3)
  - Project 46. Fam. Bakker ( Akerendamlaan 21, Beverwijk, The Netherlands; 1958-1963; Furniture ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 9, Box-folder 5:4)
  - Project 47. Mevrouw I. Fuchs ( Johannes Worpstraat 37 III, Station-Zuid WTC, Amsterdam, The Netherlands ); 1958-63; Flat ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 9, Box-folder 5:5)
  - "Sociale Academie" ( Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1959; School )
  - Project 49. "Achterhuis" ( Kromme waal, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1959; House ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 8, Box-folder 7:2)
  - Project 50. "Slaapvertrekken studie kinderhuizen" Sleeping quarters/study for children's homes ( Unknown Location; 1959; House ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 8)
  - Project 51. Dr. A. F. Hakman ( Gerrit van der Veenstraat 26, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1959; House ) (Box-folder 3:9-11, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 8)
  - Project 52. "Landelyke Stichting Clubhuizen" National Foundation Clubhouses ( Utrecht, The Netherlands; 1959; Office ) (Box-folder 3:12, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 8)
  - Project 53. W. Vermeulen ( Rustenburgerstraat 74, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1959; House ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 8)
  - Project 54. Mevrouw Groen ( Loosdrecht, The Netherlands; 1960; Summer House ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 7)
  - Project 55. Heer T. Gaastra ( Burgemeester van Tuylllaan [1], Zeist, The Netherlands; 1959-1960; House ) (Box-folder 3:13-15, Box-folder 5:15, Box-folder 7:2, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 7, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 6, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 5)
  - Project 56. "Dorpsclubhuis" Village Club House ( Jan Mankesstraat, Eerbeek, The Netherlands; 1959-1962; Clubhouse ) (Box-folder 7:2, Box-folder 3:16-28, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 4, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 3)
  - Project 57. "Kesslerhuis" ( Baarnseweg 6, Bosch en Duin, The Netherlands; 1959-1962; House ) (Box-folder 7:2, Oversize Map-Case 1/Drawer 2/Folder 10, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 2, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 4 / Folder 1)
  - Project 58. "RecreatieCentrum Kesslerhuis " ( Ymuiden, The Netherlands; 1959-1963; Recreation Center ) (Box-folder 4:1-16, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 7)
  - Project 59. Fam. A. Banting ( Willemsparkeweg 90 Apt. 2, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1959; House ) (Box-folder 4:17, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 6)
  - Project 60. Heer Lr. A. Drijver ( Akerendamlaan 15, Beverwijk, The Netherlands; 1960; House ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 6)
  - Project 61. "Vermeydenstichting" Vermeyden Foundation ( Austerlitz, The Netherlands; 1961; Nursing Home ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 6, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 5, Box-folder 4:18-20)
  - Project 62. Mejuffrouw S. van Voorst Vader ( Beethovenstraat, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1961; Furniture/ Cabnetry ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 5, Box-folder 4:21)
  - Project 63. "Clubhuis Zuid" Club House South ( Heycopstraat, Utrecht, The Netherlands; 1961; Clubhouse ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 5, Box-folder 4:22)
  - Project 64. "6 Bejaardenwoningen en 2 eengezinshuizen" 6 Elderly Homes and Two-Family Houses (Kockengen, The Netherlands; 1962: Houses ) (Box 8, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 4)
  - Project 65. Heer E. Marx ( Stadionweg 26, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1962; Interior Office ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 4, Box-folder 5:6)
  - Project 66. Mejuffrouw E. Van Hillen ( Amstel 278, Amsterdam, The Netherlands; 1962; Flat ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 4, Box-folder 5:7)
  - Project 67. Heer P. Fetter (Boulevard 28, Katwijk, The Netherlands; 1962; House ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 3, Box-folder 5:8)
  - Project 68. "Hollandse Beton Maatschappy" Dutch Concrete Society ( Groot Hertoginnelaan 258, Den Haag, The Netherlands; 1963; Typography ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 3)
  - Project 69. Mr. & Mrs. Galanter ( [2 Abby Ln], Syosset, New York, USA; 1967; Cabinetry ) (Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 2, Box-folder 5:9)
  - Project 70. Adelphi University ( Garden City, New York, USA; 1965; Fine Arts Building ) (Box-folder 5:10, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 1)
  - Project 71. "Oldebroek voor de stichting" ( Utrecht, The Netherlands; 1961-62; Conference Center ) (Box-folder 5:11, Box-folder 7:2, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 1)
  - Project 72. New York Institute of Technology ( Old Westbury, New York, USA; 1971; Painting Studios ) (Box-folder 5:72, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 1)
  - Project 73. Preliminary design for apartment in New York ( New York, USA; 1975; Apartment ) (Box-folder 5:13, Oversize Map-Case 1 / Drawer 5 / Folder 1)
  - Project 74. Vacation house (Box-folder 5:14, Box-folder 7:2)